Makiko Vaughan

(404) 374-6059 | makiko.vaughan@gmail.com | Sharpsburg, Georgia https://www.linkedin.com/in/makiko-vaughan | https://makikovaughan.github.io/myPortfolio/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Detail-oriented problem solver with 460+ training hours and experience developing full stack Java applications. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me the opportunity to excel in software development as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

W3Schools JavaScript Certification (Passed in November, 2022)

- Java
- JavaScript
- HTML (LinkedIn Badge)
- CSS
- Spring Boot

- Spring Data JPA
- Spring Security (JWT)
- Bootstrap
- REST API's
- SQL

- Unit Testing (JUnit, Mockito)
- SOLID OOP Principles
- Dependencies Injection
- Git

EXPERIENCE

Generation Junior Full Stack Java Developer Program | August 2022- December 2022 *Training Participant (in progress)*

- Participating in a 16-week, 460+ hour Junior Full Stack Java Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learning and deploying the technologies involved in creating full stack web applications with Java using Spring Boot Framework, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Implementing basic unit tests and deploying the application to Heroku

TSG USA, Inc. | Peachtree City, Georgia | July 2017 – August 2018 & June 2019 – June 2022 System Testing Engineer

- Created and conducted 100+ test cases for Panasonic Car Audio System (Honda, Toyota, and Mazda)
- Identified possible defects and its source by reading Audio Specification, then reported findings to development team
- Conducted Effectiveness confirmation tests once defects were fixed

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp | Atlanta, Georgia | September 2018 – December 2018 *Training Participant*

- Participated in a 12-week, 240+ hour Full Stack Flex Web Development that emphasizes handson class room sessions
- Learned the technologies involved in front-end and back-end (MongoDB, MySQL, Node.js, express.is)
- Received "The Most Likely to Startup" and "The Best in Class" for the last group project by

EDUCATION

Keller Graduate School of Management of DeVry University

- Master of Information Systems Management
- Cumulative GPA: 3.80/4.00
- Graduated with Distinction